艾迪  你在这里干什么
Hey Eddie. Daahh!! What're you doin' here?
没什么  室友  只是看你睡觉
Nothin' roomie, just watchin' you sleep.
为什么
Why?
让我觉得平静  请继续
Makes me feel um, peaceful, heh-heh, please.
你叫我怎么睡啊
I can't sleep now.
要不要我唱摇篮曲
You want me to sing?
听着  够了  你现在就搬
No, look, that's it, it's over, I want you out,
我要你现在就给我搬出去
I want you out of the apartment now.
你在说什么  老兄
Woah, woah, woah, what're, what're you talkin' about man.
杀人狂魔  当室友都好过你
Hannibal Lecter...better roommate than you.
我认为你这话不公平
No. See now I don't think you're being fair.
这一晚你看到我就怕了
I mean one night you see me and you get scared,
那没看到我的那些夜晚呢
I mean, what about all the other nights when you don't see me, huh?
比如说你昨天晚上起来喝水
What about last night when you went and got a drink of water
我好心躲在门后不让你看到  那又怎么说
and I was nice enough to hide behind the door, what's that about, huh?
我没想到这个
I didn't realize that.
马上给我滚
Get out now!
你真的要我出去吗
Ok, you really want me out?
对  快请
Yes please.
那我要听到你说
Ok, then I want to hear you say it,
我要听到你说  你要我出去
I want to hear you say you want me out.
我要你出去
I want you out.
不  我要听到你的嘴说
No no no, I wanna hear it from your lips.
那刚才是我的哪里跟你说的
Where did you hear it from before?
好吧  好的  我懂了
Oh, right, all right, you know what pallie I understand,
我会走  知道我会怎样吗
consider me gone, you know what
我会在你明天下班前搬出这里
I'll be out by the time you get home from work tomorrow.
-谢谢  -我听到了
- Thank you. -I heard that.
你看你  终于用时光机回到过去了
Hey. Whe-ell, look at you, finally got that time machine workin' huh?
真的  你喜欢吗
Seriously, you like it?
我在第八街跟一个家伙买的
This guy was sellin' them on 8th avenue
我看到的时候心里就想  知道我缺什么吗
and I looked at 'em and I though, you know what I don't have?
镜子
A mirror?
很好  笑吧  我觉得很时髦
Fine, make fun. I think it's jaunty.
对一个刚失业的人来说
Wow, for a guy who's recently lost his job,
你心情很好呀
you're in an awfully good mood.
不要紧的
Hey, I'll be alright.
又不是说我要从零开始
I mean it's not like I'm starting from sqare one.
我可是《我们的日子》里的
I was Dr. Drake Remoray on
德雷克·拉莫瑞医生
Days of Our Lives. Heh?
那可以算是一项储备吧
I mean that's gotta have some kind of cache.
储备  时髦
Cache? Jaunty?
钱德勒送给我"每日一词"的卫生纸
Chandler gave me word of the day toilet paper.
我要去点咖啡了
I'm gonna get some coffee.
快快快  你看了书没有啊
Oooh, so so so, did you read the book?
天啊  简直不可思议
Oh my God, it was incredible.
是不是完全说出了你的心声
Didn't it like totally speak to you?
什么书啊
Woah, woah, woah, what book is this?
瑞秋  这本书你一定要看
Rachel you have to read this book.
书名是《掌握自己的风》
It's called Be Your Own Windkeeper.
讲的是女人需要拥有更多的权力
It's about how women need to become more empowered.
对  但是有  有风
Yeah and oh, and but there's, there's wind
风能够让我们变成女神
and the wind can make us Goddesses.
知道谁夺走我们的风吗
But you know who takes out wind?
男人  他们就那样夺走了
Men, they just take it.
男人就这样夺走我们的风
Men just take out wind?
对呀  一直如此
Ya-huh, all the time,
因为他们是闪电使者
cause they are the lightning bearers.
听起来蛮酷的
Well that sounds kinda cool,
有点像《哈比人历险记》
kinda like The Hobbit.
跟《哈比人历险记》不沾边
It is nothing like The Hobbit.
就像在读我有过的每一段关系
It's like reading about every relationship I've ever had,
理查德除外
except for Richard.
理查德绝不会偷走你的风
Oh yes, no, Richard would never steal your wind.
不会
No.
因为他很可口
No, 'cause he's yummy.
对  但是其他的都会
Yes. But all the other ones.
还有  他们总是吸走
Oh yes. Oh and, the part about how they're always like
我们储存的内在能量
drinking from out pool of inner power,
但我们连尝一口都不准
but God forbid we should take a sip.
谁要吃根长条糕
Anybody want a croan.
这就是典型的闪电使者行为
Ok, this is a typical lightning-bearer thing.
就是这样  就像是
Right there, it's like, um,
你好  谁要来一根我的老二形蛋糕
'Hello, who wants one of my fallic shaped man cakes?'
你别担心了  人有祸福的
Don't worry about it already. Things happen.
所以我这次被炒鱿鱼  你不生气吗
So, you're not mad at me for getting fired and everything?
乔伊  看着我  看着我
Joey, look at me, look at me.
我的牙齿上有口红吗
Do I have lipstick on my teeth?
没有  我们说回我好不好
No, can we get back to me?
听着亲爱的  这一行到处有人被炒鱿鱼
Look honey, people get fired left and right in this business.
我已经帮你找到了
I already got you an audition
《另一个世界》的试镜机会了
for Another World.
好棒
Alright.
计程车司机乙
Cab driver number two?
不客气
You're welcome.
可是我曾经是德雷克·拉莫瑞医生
But I was Dr. Drake Remoray.
我怎么能从神经外科医生
How can I go from bein' a neurosurgeon
变成一个计程车司机
to drivin' a cab?
世事无常  随遇而安吧
Things change, roll with em.
可是他只有两句台词  这可是开倒车
But this is a two line part, it's like takin' a step backwards.
我不要演这个
I'm not gonna do this.
乔伊  这句话我也劝过
Joey, I'm gonna tell you
艾尔·明瑟和他的金字塔狗群
the same thing I told Al Minser and his pyramid of dogs.
有什么就做什么  不要随地乱搞
Take any job you can get and don't make on the floor.
抱歉  改天见
I'm sorry. See ya.
天啊
Oh, God,
天啊  我是说  这书真是...
oh, God, I mean it's just so.
没说错吧
Isn't it.
这就像是读我自己的生活
Uhh, I mean this is like reading about my own life.
我是说这书可以叫做
I mean this book could have been called
《掌握自己的风  瑞秋》
'Be Your Own Windkeeper Rachel'.
我不认为那样会畅销百万本
I don't think it would have sold a million copies
但要当礼物送给你  就太合适了
but it would have made a nice gift for you.
你们好
Hey you guys.
亲爱的  我们得走了
Uh, sweetie we've gotta go.
不
No.
不  为什么我们做任何事
No, why do we always have to do
都得照你的时间表来呢
everything according to your time table?
事实上  我们照的是电影院的时间表
Actually it's the movie theatre that has the time schedule.
这样我们才不会错过开头啊
So you don't miss the beginning.
不  这不是关于电影院
No, see this isn't about the movie theatre,
这是关于你偷了我的风
this is about you stealing my wind.
加油  妹子
You go girl.
我说不出那个味道  对吗
I can't pull that off can I?
对不起  你的风
Excuse me, your, your, your wind?
对  我的风
Yes, my wind.
你不让我吹  我怎么能成长
How do you expect me to grow if you won't let me blow?
你知道  我不会
You, you know I, I don't,
我不会
have a-
我不会反对你"吹"啊
have a problem with that.
好吧  我只是
Ok, I just,
我只是很需要
I just really need to be
自己一个人静一静
with myself right now.
很抱歉
I'm sorry.
没错  我不需要跟他道歉
You're right, I don't have to apologize.
抱歉  该死
Sorry. Damnit!
怎么了
What is it?
不知道  关于什么风呀树呀...
I, I don't know, it's got all this stuff about wind and trees
还有什么神圣的池塘
and there's some kind of sacred pool in it.
我不是很懂  但她很不高兴
I mean, I don't really get it but she's, she's pretty upset about it.
所以我不跟看书的女人约会
See, this is why I don't date women who read.
那是什么
What, what's that?
我的信用卡账单  两封里的第一封
It's my VISA bill. Envelope one of two.
不可能是好事
That can't be good.
打开来看看
Open it, open it.
天啊
Oh my God.
你看看  我怎么会花这么多钱
Look at this, how did I spend so much money?
乔伊  那只是最低还款金额
Uh Joey, that's just the minumum amount due,
总金额在这里
that's your total due.
你在"狩猎瓷场"花了三千五百块
What, woah, woah, $3500 at porcelain safari?
我的动物
My animals.
那店员说很适合我  他讲话有口音
Hey the guy said they suited me, he spoke with an accent,
我被搞迷糊了  我不知道该怎么办
I was all confused. I don't know what I'm gonna do.
我想你可以从《另一个世界》开计程车开始
Well I guess you can start by drivin a cab on Another World.
什么
What?
那个试镜
That audition.
那只有两句台词
That's a two line part.
乔伊  你欠"我爱树脂"一千一
Joey, you owe $1100 at I Love Lucite.
怎么样
So what.
所以就认命吧老兄  那是工作  有钱的
So suck it up man, it's a job, it's money.
听着  我不需要你指手画脚
Hey, look, I don't need you getting all judgemental
高高在上  卖弄学问
and condescending and pedantic.
卫生纸
Toilet paper?
没错
Yeah.
听着  我没有那样
Look, I'm not being any of those things,
我只是很实际而已
ok, I'm just being realistic.
别说了  你应该是我朋友才对
Well knock it off, you're supposed to be my friend.
我是你的朋友
I am your friend.
那你就该说  "乔伊  没事的"
Well then tell me things like, 'Joey you'll be fine,'
"坚持住"  还有
and, 'Hang in there,' and,
"你会得到大角色的  我知道"
and, 'Somethin' big's gonna come along, I know it.'
但是我不知道
But I don't know it.
我只知道你欠"缤纷世界"两千三百块
What I do know is that you owe $2300 at Isn't it Chromatic.
罗斯  我知道我欠多少
Hey Ross, I'm aware of what I owe.
那就讲一点道理啊
Ok, well then get some sense.
你奋斗了十年才得到那个角色
I mean it took you what, 10 years to get that job,
谁知道下一个机会还要等多久
who knows how long it's gonna be till you get another.
我现在不想听这个
Look, I don't wanna hear this right now.
我只是说...
Huh, I'm just saying...
那就别说"只是说"
Well don't just say.
或许我该走了
Ya know, maybe, maybe I should just go.
好的
Okay.
好  咱们回头见
Ok. I'll see ya later.
你考虑看看
Just think about it, ok.
我不需要考虑
I don't need to think about it.
我曾经是德雷克·拉莫瑞医生
I was Dr. Drake Remoray.
那是大角色
That was huge.
大机会还会出现的  你等着瞧
Big things are gonna happen, you'll see.
罗斯  你走了吗
Ross, you still there?
你好  伙计
Hey, pal.
艾迪  你还在这里干什么
Eddie what're you still doin' here?
只是在做一些脱水水果及蔬菜
Ah, just some basic dehydrating of a few fruits and vegetables.
老天爷  这玩意儿太棒了
Man alive this thing's fantastic!
艾迪  你有没有忘记什么事
Look Eddie, aren't you forgetting anything?
对了  看  我买了一条新的金鱼
Oh yeah, that's right, look I got us a new goldfish.
它比上一条活泼多了
He's a lot feistier that the last one.
大概是因为上一条是饼干公司做的吧
Maybe 'cause the last one was made by Pepperidge Farm.
艾迪  现在是不是有件事
Look Eddie, isn't there something else
你必须要马上去做的
you're supposed to be doing right now?
除非是跟脱水扯上关系的  老兄
Well, not unless it's got something to do with dehydrating my man
因为现在我是脱水疯子
because right now I'm a dehydrating maniac!
你就当做件好事吧
Look you have to help me out here.
我以为我们讲好了  我以为这时候...
I thought we had a deal. I thought by the time...
你知道这是什么吗
Ah-ah-ah, you know what that is?
你上个室友的肾
Your last roommate's kidney?
这是一颗番茄  这个一定要拿来当摆饰
That's a tomato. This one definitely goes in the display.
甘瑟  我要柠檬水外带
Hey Gunther, let me get a lemonade to go.
柠檬水  你没事吧
Lemonade? You ok man?
只是事业不太顺利
Ah, it's career stuff.
不知道你听说没  我演的角色被编剧写死了
I don't know if you heard but they killed off my character on the show.
真不幸  怎么死的
Oh, that's too bad. How'd they do it?
我掉下了电梯井
I fell down an elevator shaft.
真惨  我是雪崩的时候被活埋的
That sucks. I was buried in an avalanche.
什么
What?
我以前演过《我的孩子们》里的布莱斯
I used to be Bryce on All My Children.
干嘛大家都要看我睡觉
Why must everybody watch me sleep?
不准再看我睡觉了  不准再看
There'll be no more watching me sleep, no more watching.
我...
I wa-
看看  我有些好东西要脱水哦
Hey man, check it out, I got some great stuff to dehydrate here.
我有葡萄  还有杏子
I got some grapes, got some apricots,
我想这些水球
I thought it would be really cool
脱水后的样子一定很酷
to see what happens with these water balloons.
出去  出去  出去...
Get out. Get out, get out, get out, get out, get out, get out.
什么
What?
你搬出去  带着水果
You, move out. Take your fruit,
你的烂水果  给我搬出去
your stupid small fruit and get out!
你要我搬出去吗
You, you want, you want me to move out?
是啊
Uh-huh.
我得告诉你  老兄
I uh, I gotta tell you man,
这有点突如其来  你不认为吗
I mean, that's uh, it's kinda out of the blue, I mean don't you think?
这不是突如其来
This is not out of the blue,
都已经来了好久了
this is smack dab in the middle of the blue.
放轻松  别激动  兄弟
Relax, take it easy buddy.
别重申了  要我走是吗
Tell me twice, you want me to go?
好吧  好吧  我回头再来拿东西
Alright, alright, guess I'll be back for my stuff.
不过你以为我会让我的鱼跟你独处
But if you think for one second I'm leaving you alone with my fish,
那你就疯了
you're insane Jack!
要我帮忙吗
You want some help.
不用了  小子
No help required Chico.
一直开到机场吗
All the way to the airport huh?
那可是超过三十英里了
You know that's over 30 miles,
估计得要"丑"十块
that's gonna cost you about so bucks.
抱歉  应该是五十块
Excuse me, that's 50 bucks.
什么
What?
五加零
Five oh dollars.
你知道为什么吗
Ohh, you know what it is?
因为是传真的所以不清楚
It's smudgy 'cause they're fax pages.
我在《我们的日子》里
Now when I was on Days of Our Lives
演德雷克·拉莫瑞医生时
as Dr. Drake Remoray,
他们会送来打印的整个剧本
they'd send over the whole script on real paper and everything.
那太棒了
That's great.
顺便说下
And, and just so you know,
如果你想加长这场戏
if you wanted to expand this scene like,
像是出车祸之类的  我可以照顾伤患
like have the cab crash or somethin', I could attend to the victims
因为我有出演医务剧的背景
'cause I have a background in medical acting.
好吧  感谢你前来试镜
Ok, listen, thanks for coming in.
不  别谢谢我来
No no, uh, don't thank me for comin' in.
至少让我演完吧
Uh, at least let me finish.
我们可以走高速公路  但是
Uh, we could take the expressway but uh,
这个时段  还是走"轿"比较好一点
this time of day you're better off taking the budge.
你们的意思是"桥"  对不对
You were goin' for the word bridge there weren't ya.
祝我今天愉快
I'll have a good day.
第28个问题
Ok, question number 28,
你有没有让闪电使者  夺走过你的风
have you ever allowed a lighning bearer to take your wind?
我得说  没有
I would have to say no.
而我得说  "瞎说"
And I would have to say pah-huh.
什么嘛
What?
你不记得那个演木偶戏的吗
Do you not remember the puppet guy?
对  你完全让他在你的
Yeah you like totally let him wash his feet
内在能量池里大洗其脚呀
in the pool of your inner power.
还有他的木偶
And his puppet too.
好吧  但至少我不会在第一次约会
Yeah ok, well at least I didn't let some guy
就让人家进入我的正义真理的森林
into the forest of my righteous truth on the first date.
谁啊
Who?
保罗
Paul.
好啦好啦  继续  继续下一个
Ok, ok, ok, moving on, moving on, next question.
第29题  你曾经为一个闪电使者
Ok number 29, have you ever betrayed another goddess
背叛过另一位女神吗
for a lightning bearer?
第30题
Ok, number 30.
搞什么  回到第29题
Woah, woah, woah, let's go back to 29.
就我记得的没有
Not uh, not to my recollection.
丹尼·艾夏克  高一
Huuh, alright, Danny Arshak, ninth grade.
瑞秋  你知道那瓶子完全指向我的
Oh, c'mon Rach, you know the bottle was totally pointing at me.
那是因为你的体积太庞大了
Only 'cause you took up half the circle.
听你们两个说的  真是悲哀
Listen to you two. It's so sad.
看来我要一个人去参加女神会议了
Looks like I'm gonna be going to the goddess meetings alone.
想得美  她们会发现杰森·赫利甩了
Well not when they find out you slept with Jason Hurley
莫妮卡一小时后  你就跟他上床了
an hour after he broke up with Monica.
才一小时
That was only an hour?
你可真是个吹落叶机
You are such a leaf blower.
小心这个3D的"最后的晚餐"
Oh hey uh, be careful with that 3-D last supper,
犹大有点松了
Judas is a little loose.
老天  这怎么回事
Oh my God, what's goin' on?
他们来拿回东西  我想你说得对
They're takin all my stuff back. I guess you were right.
不  我不对  我就是来告诉你这个的
No look I wasn't right, that's what I came here to tell you.
因为那天我的心
I was totally hung up on,
完全在我自己的事情上
on my own stuff the other day.
听着  我是个需要安全感的人
Listen, I'm someone who needs the whole security thing, ya know.
我需要知道
To know exactly
下次薪水从哪儿来  但你不同
where my next paycheck is coming from buy you,
你不需要  我觉得你真了不起
you don't need that and that's amazing to me.
我永远都无法像你这样  乔伊
I could never do what you do Joey.
谢了  罗斯
Thanks Ross.
而且你应该等待更大的机会
Yeah. And you should hold out for something bigger.
你不知道我多么敬重
I can't tell you how much respect I have for you
你不去那个计程车司机的烂试镜
not going to that stupid cab driver audition.
我去了
I went.
太棒了  结果呢
Great, how did it go?
没成
I didn't get it.
真有你的
Good for you.
什么
What?
太棒了
You're livin' the dream.
好吧
All right then.
别拿走鹦鹉
Oh, not my parrot.
我看不下去了
I can't watch this.
等等
Hey hold on, hold on.
要多少钱  救那只鸟要多少钱
How much for the uh, how much to save the bird?
一千二
1200.
美金吗  你花一千二百美金买只塑胶鸟
Dollars? You spent $1200 dollars on a plastic bird?
那是一时冲动  它在收银机附近
Uhhh, I was an impulse buyer, near the register.
走吧  把鸟带走吧
Go ahead, go ahead with the bird.
有没有大约两百左右的
Ok, do you have anything for around 200?
那只狗
The dog.
我买了  送给你  老兄
I'll take it. My gift to you man.
谢了  罗斯
Thanks Ross.
不过我真的很喜欢那只鸟
I really like that bird though...
可这狗...
But the dog...
你们的蛋糕
Here are your cakes.
我们没点蛋糕
We didn't order cake.
我知道  是我请的
No, I know, they're from me.
听着  两位  这样不好
Look you guys this is not good.
被男人偷走我们的风  就够惨了
I mean we have enough trouble with guys stealing our wind
何苦再自相残杀呢
without taking it from each other.
你说得对
You're right.
是吧
You know.
我爱你  女神们
I love you goddesses.
我也爱你们
I love you.
我再也不会吸走你们的风了
I don't ever want to suck your wind again.
谢谢  我们和好了吗
Thank you. So are we good?
和好了
We're good.
We're good?
是的
Yeah.
那我把蛋糕送回去
Ok, let me take these cakes back
否则会从我薪水里扣的
'cause they're gonna take that out of my paycheck.
叮当  那个疯子走了
Ding dong, the psycho's gone.
这次你确定吗
Are you sure this time?
对  我亲眼看到他离开的
Yes, yes I actually saw him leave.
那家伙拿着一个人头站在窗口
I mean that guy is standing in the window holding a human head.
他拿着一个人头站在窗口
He is standing in the window holding a human head!
你瞧老兄
Check it out man,
我在梅西百货后面巷子的模特上摘下来的
I tore it off some mannaquin in the alley behind Macy's.
梅西百货后面没有巷子
There is no alley behind Macy's.
我在少女服装部摘的  有什么大不了的
So I got it in the junior miss department, big diff.
你瞧瞧老兄  我们下次的鸡尾酒会
Anyway check it out man, it's gonna make a hell of a conversation
就有话题聊了  是吧伙计
piece at out next cocktail party, huh pal?
我们下次的鸡尾酒会
Our next cocktail party?
对呀  可以放薯片在里面
Yeah, you know, put chips in it,
弄成一个薯片小妞
we'll make like a chip chick.
艾迪  你记得昨天的事吗
Eddie, do you remember yesterday?
我想我模模糊糊地记得
Uh yes, I think I vaguely recall it.
你还记得昨天跟我说过话吗
Do you remember talking to me yesterday?
当然
Yes.
发生了什么事
So what happened?
我们开车去赌城啊  老兄
We took a road trip to Las Vegas man.
我的天啊
Oh sweet Moses.
那么这次的旅行  你们有没有赢钱呢
So on this road trip, did you guys win any money?
没有  我输光了
Naah, I crapped out,
但这位21点先生赢了三百
but Mr. 21 over here he cleans up, 300 bucks,
瞧  他买了这双新鞋给我  很棒吧
check it out he buys me these new shoes, sweet huh?
不错
Nice.
咱们楼上见了  再见了各位
Yeah. Well see ya upstairs. See ya pals.
还有别人开始很喜欢他了吗
Is anyone else starting to really like him?
需要我效劳吗
May I help you?
我的钥匙为什么不能用了
Why doesn't my key work and
我的东西为什么都在楼下
what's all my stuff doin' downstairs?
抱歉
Well, I'm, I'm sorry...
我们有见过吗
Have we met?
我是艾迪  你这个变态  我是你室友
It's Eddie you freak, your roommate.
对不起  可我已经有室友了
I, I'm sorry, I uh I already have a roommate.
你好
Hello.
他住这里很多年了
Yeah, he's lived here for years,
我不知道你在说什么  老兄
I don't, I don't know what you're talking about man.
他搬出去以后我才搬进来的
No he, he moved out and I moved in.
如果是那样的话  我们应该记得才对
Well I, I think we'd remember something like that.
我知道我会的
I know I would.
说的有道理
Well that's uh, that's a good point.
那好吧  我想我记错房子了
Um ok, well, uh, I guess I got the wrong apartment then.
两位  对不起  非常抱歉
I, I'm, look, I'm, ya know, I'm sorry, I'm terriably sorry.
没关系
Hey no problem.
再见了
See ya.
再会了  脱水水果疯子
Goodbuy you fruit drying psychopath.
要我帮你收拾行李吗
So you want me to help you unpack your stuff?
不用了  我只是想让你知道
Na, na I'm ok. Oh and uh, just so you know,
我不是不得已才搬回来的
I'm not movin' back in 'cause I have to.
是不得已没错
Well, I mean, I do have to.
但是那个地方并不是真的...
It's just that that place wasn't really,
这里...
I mean, this is...
欢迎回家  老兄
Welcome home man.
小试一下身手
A little foos?
没问题
Absolutely.
这颗球怎么了
What happened to the foosball?
那是颗哈蜜瓜
Ah that's a cantaloupe.
每次罗斯来  我们都要
Hey look, are we gonna have to bring this out
把这玩意拖出来吗
every time Ross comes over?
他付了很多钱买的
He paid a lot of money for it.
我要换个方式抬
I'm gonna hold him a different way.
我不明白  既然你这么讨厌它
Look I don't understand, if you hated it so much,
那当初为何要买呢
why did you buy it in the first place?
我那边有一整个陶瓷动物园嘛
Well, I had a whole ceramic zoo thing goin' over there but
现在少了其它动物  看起来就很俗了
now, without the other ones, it just looks tacky.
它要带出去大便吗  还是会在家
So is he housetrained or is he gonna leave
到处留下小瓷器便便
little bathroom tiles all over the place?
别动
Stay.
Stay!
好假狗
Good fake dog.